var list = [
    {
        id: "Q1",
        question: "How early do you get up in the morning?",
        answers: ["Crack of dawn", "Early", "9am", "Later", "I don't have enough alarms"],
        images: ["https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100"]
    },
    {
        id: "Q2",
        question: "When do you go to bed?",
        answers: ["Before the monsters come out","Before midnight","Later on weekends","1AM","I don't"],
        images: ["https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100"]
    },
    {
        id: "Q3",
        question: "Favorite kind of movie?",
        answers: ["Action","Comedy","Sci-Fi","History","DEMONS DEMONS DEMONS"],
        images: ["https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100"]
    },
    {
        id: "Q4",
        question: "Favorite alcoholic beverage?",
        answers: ["Hennessy", "Whiskey", "Schnaaps", "Wine", "Beer", "Cider", "Milk", "Water"],
        images: ["https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100"]
    },
    {
        id: "Q5",
        question: "Favorite gainz meal?",
        answers: ["Chicken and Biscuits", "Dark Matter and CafeMac Chicken Breasts", "Protein Powder", "Chicken Pasta with Spinach","Steak", "Tuna", "Macaroni & Cheese with Steak", "Chicken and Brocoli"],
        images: ["https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100"]
    },
    {
        id: "Q6",
        question: "Favorite lift?",
        answers: ["Cleans", "Squat", "Curls", "Pull-ups", "Bench", "Power Clean and Front Squat"],
        images: ["https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100"]
    },
    {
        id: "Q7",
        question: "Major?",
        answers: ["Neuroscience", "Chemistry", "Economics", "Psychology", "Physics", "Computer Science"],
        images: ["https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100"]
    },
    {
        id: "Q8",
        question: "Favorite hobby?",
        answers: ["Roasting people", "Hockey", "Making Gainz", "Online Strategy Games", "Anything outside", "Playing instruments", "Reading", "Gargling Mouthwash"],
        images: ["https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100"]
    },
    {
        id: "Q9",
        question: "Favorite book?",
        answers: ["What's a book?", "Dragon Teeth by Michael Crichton", "The Great Gatsby by F. Scott Fitzgerald", "Airman by Eoin Colfer", "A Storm of Swords by George R.R. Martin","The Bible", "The Demon King by Cinda Williams Chima", "When Breath Becomes Air by Paul Kalanithi"],
        images: ["https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100"]
    },
    {
        id: "Q10",
        question: "What's your anthem?",
        answers: ["Alright by Kendrick Lamar", "The Distance by Cake", "Sunday Candy by Chance the Rapper", "Rose Tattoo by Dropkick Murphys", "Bohemian Rhapsody", "Sweet Home Alabama", "The National Anthem", "Shake your Rump to the Funk by the Bar Kays"],
        images: ["https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100","https://via.placeholder.com/100x100"]
    }
];

var questions = {
    list: list
};

module.exports = questions;